[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The song featured in the sound clip is Bark at the Moon, a 1983 recording by this artist who often incorporated elements of the horror genre in his music and stage presence.", "correct_answer": "Ozzy Osbourne", "incorrect_answers": ["Ted Nugent", "Ronnie James Dio", "Alice Cooper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country was coffee first roasted and brewed?", "correct_answer": "Ethiopia", "incorrect_answers": ["Brasil", "Zimbabwe", "Indonesia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2008 movie received 13 nominations at the 81st Academy Awards 2009?", "correct_answer": "The Curious Case of Benjamin Button", "incorrect_answers": ["Slumdog Millionaire", "Milk", "The Reader"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the pub in which the characters barricade themselves in the 2004 movie Shaun of the Dead?", "correct_answer": "Winchester", "incorrect_answers": ["Knotingham", "Howitzer", "Dorchester"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What made James Cameron start working on the 1997 movie masterpiece Titanic?", "correct_answer": "He was greatly interested in shipwrecks.", "incorrect_answers": ["He had a nightmare about the sinking of Titanic.", "All of these", "He wanted to make a movie which would star Leonardo DiCaprio and Kate Winslet."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many times has Ernest Borgnine been married?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "3", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is what Barbie Doll is made of.", "correct_answer": "Polyvinyl Chloride", "incorrect_answers": ["Polyester", "Rubber", "Nylon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This flower, often associated with narcissism and egoism in art, is the national flower of Wales.", "correct_answer": "Daffodil", "incorrect_answers": ["Carnation", "Lily", "Violet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the three-letter acronym for the Nobel-winning process which allows DNA to be amplified?", "correct_answer": "PCR", "incorrect_answers": ["HCV", "ATP", "SRC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these types of fat raises both LDL(bad cholesterol) and HDL(good cholesterol)?", "correct_answer": "Saturated", "incorrect_answers": ["Trans", "Monounsaturated", "Polyunsaturated"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This bloody battle, a turning point in World War II, was won by the Soviets in 1943.", "correct_answer": "Battle of Stalingrad", "incorrect_answers": ["Battle of Leningrad", "Battle of Moscow", "Battle of Kiev"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the vampire portrayed by Tom Cruise in the 1994 movie Interview with the Vampire: The Vampire Chronicles?", "correct_answer": "Lestat", "incorrect_answers": ["Leviathan", "Armand", "Lucifer"]}]